{"data":[{"question":"It is essential that cancer ________ diagnosed and treated as early as possible in order to assure a successful cure.","a":"is","b":"been","c":"was","d":"be","answer":"4","explain":"\n- It's important\/essential that somebody do something.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Products in this shop were ________ arranged, displayed, presented on the shelves.","a":"attract","b":"attractive","c":"attraction","d":"attractively","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Adverb can be used to modify adjective, normal verb.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The battle field was a ________ sight.","a":"fear","b":"fearsome","c":"fearlessly","d":"fearless","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Fearsome: very frightening.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"A vine climbs from one tree to another, continuing to grow and support itself even when the original supporting tree is ________ longer alive.","a":"no","b":"not","c":"any more","d":"none","answer":"1","explain":"\n- No longer: used when something used to happen or be true in the past but does not happen or is not true now.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Parents have great ________ for their children's future.","a":"expectant","b":"expectancies","c":"expects","d":"expectations","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Great + noun.\u00a0\n- Expectation: what you think or hope will happen.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The consistency of protoplasm and that of glue ________.","a":"they are alike","b":"are similar to","c":"are similar","d":"the same","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To be similar = to be the same.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The lights and appliances in most homes use alternating current ________.","a":"instead direct current","b":"instead of direct current","c":"that instead direct current","d":"for direct current instead","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Instead of: used to say what is not used, does not happen etc, when something else is used, happens.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"When Franklin Roosevelt decided to run for a fourth term, the opposition said that he was ________.","a":"so old","b":"too old","c":"oldest","d":"very older","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Too + adj to do sth: impossible to do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The decomposition of microscopic animals at the bottom of the sea results in an accumulation of ________ in porous rocks.","a":"the oil","b":"oil","c":"an oil","d":"oils","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Oil is uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- Not using article: Before a common noun used in its commonest sense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"They discussed the matter calmly and ________.","a":"reason","b":"reasoned","c":"reasonable","d":"reasonably","answer":"4","explain":"\n - Normal verb (discuss)+ adv.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"}]}